Guide to the photograph album Royal Flying Corps - Egypt in the 1910s AD.MC.014
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Left: A portrait of a woman with a child. Right: An individual portrait of a man, Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000075; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Women; Children; Girls; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Men; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Jewelry; Workers; Niqab
- An empty page., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000076; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
- Left: People walking beneath an arch. Right: A street vendor., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000077; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Men; Architecture; Doors/Entrances; Street Vendors; Group Portraits; Palm Trees; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Turbans; Regional/National Dress; Boys; Streets/Roads; Girls; Women
- An empty page., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000078; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
- A portrait of a woman., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000079; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Women; Jewelry; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Egypt; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
- An empty page., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000080; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
- Left: Two women, one of whom holds a child. Right: Two women standing in water, balancing pots on their heads., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000081; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Women; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Water; Children; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Pottery; Nile River; Buildings
- An empty page., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000082; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
- Top: A man walking with a camel near the Great Pyramids. Bottom: A boy herding sheep., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000083; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Men; Boys; Children; Sheep; Animals; Palm Trees; Rivers; Water; Individual Portraits; Giza, Egypt; Pyramids; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Streets/Roads; Camels; Egypt
- An empty page., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000084; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
- A portrait of a man weaing a turban., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000085; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Men; Individual Portraits; Turbans; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Regional/National Dress
- An empty page., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000086; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
- From top left clockwise: A man talking to a boy, a man carrying a basket on his head containing bread products, a man riding a dobkey and camels carrying supplies, and a portrait of two boys in front of a building., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000087; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Boys; Children; Fezes/Tarbouches; Food; Men; Individual Portraits; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Air Force; Regional/National Dress; Donkeys; Camels; Animals; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Street Vendors
- An empty page., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000088; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
- Top: A portrait of a man working at an irrigation device with two soldiers standing nearby. Middle: Two girls sitting on the ground. Bottom: A portrait of seven children., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000089; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Irrigation; Agriculture/Farms; Men; Uniforms; Air Force; Military/Soldiers; Girls; Children; Boys; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Canes/Walking Sticks
- From top left clockwise: A woman holding two dogs on leads in front of some tea rooms, three portraits of dogs and a man holding a dog on a lead., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000090; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Dogs; Animals; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Women; Men; Individual Portraits; Hats; Architecture; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Restaurants/bars; England, UK
- From top to bottom: Street vendors and passersby, two men seated on the ground, and a portrait of a man and a boy with a mule., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000091; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Street Vendors; Men; Boys; Children; Boats/Ships; Water; Donkeys; Animals; Streets/Roads; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Transportation; Rivers; Nile River; Turbans; Regional/National Dress
- Three portraits of dogs., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000092; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Dogs; Group Portraits; Animals; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; England, UK; Gardens
- From top left clockwise: A boy standing outdoors, a soldier, a side profile of a camel, and men loading soacks onto docked boats., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000093; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Boys; Children; Men; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Air Force; Camels; Animals; Individual Portraits; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Nile River; Rivers; Water; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Facial Hair; Canes/Walking Sticks; Medals/Insignia
- Top: Portraits of a man and a woman with a dog. Bottom: Two portraits of the same man., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000094; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Women; Dogs; Animals; Men; Hats; Individual Portraits; Gardens; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; England, UK; Facial Hair; Clocks/Watches; Buildings
- Portraits of soldiers with guns., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000095; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Men; Uniforms; Bridges; Military/Soldiers; Air Force; Outdoors; Guns; Weapons; Group Portraits; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Deserts; Mountains/Hills
- From top left clockwise: A woman sitting on a stile, a woman standing in a field, a woman and a dog in a garden, and two women sitting on a log., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000096; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Canes/Walking Sticks; Women; Hats; Dogs; Animals; Group Portraits; Gardens; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; England, UK; Bags/Purses; Jewelry; Countryside/Rural; Canes/Walking Sticks
- From top left: A soldier standing by a shoreline, two group portraits of soldiers sitting on the ground, and soldiers standing on a dredger., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000097; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Smoking; Beaches; Water; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Air Force; Group Portraits; Men; Machines; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Smoking; Coast; Canes/Walking Sticks; Nile River
- From top left clockwise: A woman holding a dog, soldiers sitting in deck chairs around a table outdoors, two women at the beach, and a woman sitting on the ground., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000098; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Women; Dogs; Animals; Gardens; Countryside/Rural; Individual Portraits; Hats; Group Portraits; Men; Tea/Coffee; Uniforms; Air Force; Military/Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Water; Beaches; England, UK; Bags/Purses; Picnic
- Three views of soldiers in a punt boat., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000099; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Men; Boats/Ships; Rivers; Water; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Air Force; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; England, UK; Transportation
- Portraits of a women and a man in a garden., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000100; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Gardens; England, UK; Men; Women; Facial Hair; Dogs; Animals; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Bags/Purses; Countryside/Rural; Individual Portraits; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Top: A man stands at the edge of a lake. Middle and bottom: Two landscape views of a lake., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000101; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Men; Facial Hair; Hats; Lakes; Individual Portraits; England, UK; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes
- Individual portraits of a man and woman adjacent to landscape views of cliffs., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000102; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Men; Women; Animals; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits; Mountains/Hills; Streets/Roads; Gardens; Countryside/Rural; Dogs; England, UK; Photographic Prints; Hats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Clocks/Watches; Europe; Coast
- Three views of stream and a stately house in front of a lake., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000103; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Water; Houses; Buildings; Lakes; Forest/Woodlands; England, UK; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Three views of a coastal landscape, a stone bridge across a body of water and a woman at a beach., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000104; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Coast; Beaches; Water; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Bridges; England, UK; Women; Hats; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Landscapes; Newspapers/Magazines; Houses; Mountains/Hills
- Three views of the coastline in Hastings, including the Chatsworth Hotel., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000105; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Coast; Beaches; Water; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Buildings; Architecture; Hotels; Crowds; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Hastings, England, UK; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Umbrellas/Parasols; Flags
- From top left clockwise: a bridge over a river, a woman standing in front of a building, two mountain landscapes, and a photograph of a boat going down a river., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000106; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Bridges; Water; Rivers; Women; Restaurants/bars; Buildings; Hats; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; England, UK; Carriages/Coaches; Cattle/Cows; Animals; Houses
- Five landscapes., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_n000107; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
  Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Agriculture/Farms; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; England, UK
- An empty page., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_zbk01; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
- The back inside cover for the album 'Royal Flying Corps - Egypt in the 1910s'., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_zbk02; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
- The back inside cover for the album 'Royal Flying Corps - Egypt in the 1910s'., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_zbk03; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
- The back inside cover for the album 'Royal Flying Corps - Egypt in the 1910s'., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_zbk04; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)
- The back cover of the album 'Royal Flying Corps - Egypt in the 1910s'., Circa 1910-1918; nyuad_pa000004_zbk05; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_014)